Hello.
こんにちは
You're in good spirits.
元気がいいですね
is that so.
そうですか
May I ask your name?
お名前聞いてもいいですか?
Yes, it's Yayoi.
はい、やよいです
Yayoi-chan.
やよいちゃん
What do you usually do?
普段は何してる人ですか?
I'm going to university.
大学に行ってます
university student?
大学生?
yes.
はい
She's a female college student.
女子大生ですね
I agree.
そうですね
yes.
はい
Are you busy studying?
勉強が忙しいですか?
I agree.
そうですね
It's already this time of year.
もうこの時期になっちゃうと
Did you come to the hotel?
ホテルに来てくれたんですか?
I'm a little short on money.
ちょっとお金困っちゃってる
You're in trouble.
困っちゃってるんですね
Please cooperate
ご協力して
Can you ask me where I'm going?
いく こと聞いてくれますか?
yes.
はい
Yes, I'll do my best.
はい、頑張ります
Will you learn these things?
そういったこと学んでくれるの?
yes.
はい
What's going on?
どうなってる?
I'm feeling very lonely.
すごく孤独になってる
Chin-chan, do you want to lick it?
チンちゃん、舐めたい?
yes.
はい
I asked her to let me lick her.
舐めさせてくださいってお願いして
Please let me lick it.
舐めさせてください
What about Chimp?
チンプはどう?
チンプはどうですか?
I'm glad it was so big.
すごく大きくてよかったね
How does it compare to your boyfriend Chimp?
彼氏のチンプと比べてどう?
This one is bigger.
こっちのほうが大きい
How different?
どれくらい違う?
3x.
3倍
Three times?
3倍?
Does your jaw get tired?
あごが疲れちゃいますか?
I'm tired.
疲れちゃう
Thank you for trying a little harder.
もうちょっと頑張ってくれて
This big old man has never been crazy.
この大きいおじいちゃんって いかれたことない
Okay, then stand up for a moment.
はい、じゃあちょっと立ってみて
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Your jaw is a little tired, right?
あごはちょっと疲れちゃったでしょ?
Well then, let's move on to the next one.
じゃあちょっと次はさ
Well then, that's all for now.
それじゃあこれぐらいにして、しこしこ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels so good, doesn't it?
すご く気持ちいいでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels so good.
すごく気持ちいい
I'll just say it feels good.
気持ちいいって言っちゃうよ、それ
what?
何?
Have you ever licked it?
舐めたことある?
Can I have you lick me?
舐めてもらっていい?
yes.
はい
How do I use it? If I lick it?
どうやって使うだろう、舐めば?
For your first experience.
初めての体験に
You can lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めていいからね
Licking and sucking.
舐めたり、吸ったりして
Let's lick it while squeezing it.
しこしこしながら舐めてみましょうか
Use it lightly.
軽くに使って
yes.
はい
It feels good.
気持ちいいですね
I'll become a better person.
高まった方になるんで
Can I have some food?
食べてもらっていい?
yes.
はい
This is how it is.
こうなってるんで
It's harder than before, right?
さっきより硬くなってるでしょ?
Is it harder than before?
さ っきより硬くなってる?
It's harder than before.
さっきより硬くなってる
I want to go inside.
中に入れたい
Do you want to enter?
入れたい?
I want to enter.
入 れたい
Can you do it only here?
ここだけできる?
want?
欲しい?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
want.
欲しい
do you want?
欲しいですか?
Shall I ask you a favor?
お願いしてみようか
Please enter it.
入 れてください
Please put your dick in.
ちんちん入れてください
want?
欲しい?
This is it.
これが
I want it.
欲しいです
It's not a stock, but is that okay?
株式じゃないけどいいの?
That's interesting.
面白いですね
Stop it.
やめちゃって
I'll call you.
呼びますんで
Add glass frequently.
頻繁にガラス入れましょうよ
Well then, thank you very much for today.
じゃあ今日はありがとうございました
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました